const flashcards = [
  {
    question: "a",
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    question: "c",
    answer: "d",
  },
  {
    question: "e",
    answer: "f",
  },
  {
    question: "g",
    answer: "h",
  },
  {
    question: "i",
    answer: "j",
  },
  {
    question: "k",
    answer: "l",
  },
  {
    question: "m",
    answer: "n",
  },
  {
    question: "o",
    answer: "p",
  },
  {
    question: "q",
    answer: "r",
  },
  {
    question: "s",
    answer: "t",
  },
]

export default flashcards;